SOKULAPALEM
Everyone's story starts with a mother.
So does mine.
Chinnu…
Do you know what true anger means?
PROLOGUE
Hey, why are you being a baby?
You heard the doctor.
No matter what we do,
I won't make it past two months.
It is what it is.
You've done beyond your potential.
What more can you do?
This is just my fate.
Can I get through life without you?
When I think of our kids…
I get worried about their future.
Don't tell them yet.
First, let me tell them
how to take on life.
We can tell them slowly later.
Your son needs…
most of the talking.
He beat someone up again.
If he repeats this…
they'll rusticate him from school.
I wonder where all his anger comes from.
Where else?
If you're Chayadevi,
your son is Suryakantham.
He's gone after his feisty mother.
Hey!
Hey, brother-in-law!
Send Chaya out!
Seethapathi.
My uncle.
They're our only relatives.
My aunt, Prabhavathi.
And her daughter Kalyani.
Kallu for short.
My Kallu.
She doesn't like me one bit.
Reason being…
my anger.
Surya!
He used to come home drunk
and beat up my aunt every day.
So my mom made his wife file a
complaint against her own brother.
She sent him to jail.
I'll not spare you!
But she knew that wasn't the solution.
So, without anyone's knowledge…
she wanted to send them to another city.
Kallu didn't say a word
to me before leaving.
She didn't even give me a chance
to tell her how much I love her.
-Come on out!
-You're creating a havoc every day!
-You're enjoying with your spouse at home.
-What is it?
I'm roaming on the streets like an orphan.
You…
Answer me!
Hey, mind your language!
You went to jail and
you're still as barbaric.
-Yes, I am!
-Hey!
What's with this drama every day?
We're not able to sleep.
She sent my wife and daughter away.
Tell her to give me their address.
Tell him where they are.
He'll take them home.
-I don't know.
-Come on! He's your brother.
He's not my brother.
I don't have a brother.
I have nothing to do with this man.
I don't care if you hit him
or report him to the police.
Come inside.
-Do whatever the hell you want.
-You don't know me?
-Get out of here!
-Let me go!
-Tell me where my wife and daughter are!
-Hey!
Why do you want extra
trouble in this situation?
Just tell him where they are.
They're living safely and
independently. Let them.
You saw what he does to them.
I'll break his legs! Take him away!
No, listen to me.
No matter what anyone says,
I won't reveal their whereabouts.
Not even to you.
Where did he go?
Come.
Tired, already?
You can't just hit people
when you're angry.
Is there no other way?
That's the only way I know.
Chinnu, look at me.
If you lose your temper for everything,
your anger will have no meaning.
Your anger needs to have a purpose.
A reason.
Am I right?
There is a reason, Mom.
Uncle called you--
Will you listen to your mom?
Come.
Let's dedicate a day to your anger.
What do you mean?
Well, you can't express
your anger every day.
A dedicated day for your anger.
One day a week.
No matter how furious you are,
you can express it only on that one day.
Even if it gets tough on the other days,
you should control your anger somehow.
Why so?
Because more than half the instances
that make you angry are pointless.
So whenever you feel angry,
pause for a while, think about it,
and if you still feel the
same anger towards them,
you can express it on that one day.
Okay?
Promise me.
I can express it on that one day, right?
My sweetheart!
Tell me which day that is.
From now on,
whenever you feel angry,
you come to me and tell me.
The day your anger is truly justified,
I won't say a word.
That day, you do what you want.
Okay?
With the patience
And affection of an angel
Just because you learned to cook,
doesn't mean you live in the kitchen.
This is just another subject like
the ones you have in school.
Understood?
Let me taste it.
It's yummy.
Mom, today?
What happened?
Rakesh spilled ink on my shirt.
Tell me, is today the day?
WEDNESDAY
Wednesday is always a…
A journey of hope that goes on forever
Mom, today?
MONDAY
If you strike off every day,
how do I control my anger, Mom?
You've been reading the
same lesson for four days.
What lesson is it?
Deepavali.
I have an idea.
"There lived a demon called
Narakasur in the olden days.
He used to trouble people a lot.
So, Sri Krishna teamed up
with Satyabhama and killed him."
It's the beginning of a new spring
Silence brings this sweet agony
There lived a demon called
Narakasur in the olden days.
He used to trouble people a lot.
So Sri Krishna teamed up
with Satyabhama and killed him!
What's with these stupid
scribbles on the wall?
Whack him a couple of times
and all his anger will come down.
You can't expect change
without a seed of hope.
You're only thinking about the one
day he's going to express his anger.
I'm thinking about the six days
when he won't cross the line.
I'm worried about him
exploding on that one day,
after holding it in for so long.
I don't get this
"angry one day a week" thing.
Chinnu…
Do you know what true anger means?
Chinnu?
I didn't listen to what
she said that night.
And I didn't know that I
would never hear it again.
Mom…
Mom, get up!
She's dead!
-Hey!
-Go away!
Go away! Don't create a scene!
Get out of here!
Enough of your nuisance!
I don't care really.
But where did you send
my wife and little girl?
You witch!
Bloody witch, get up!
Get up!
Have you lost your mind?
She's your sister, damn it!
When will you change?
Mom, today?
FRIDAY
SATURDAY
Mom…
Transition…
Origin…
Arrival…
The day your anger is truly justified,
I won't say a word.
You do whatever you want.
SATURDAY
Okay?
He, the one who breaks
The shackles of doubt
With a fierce and intense gaze
His nails are like blazing
Flames on a mountain
He is the constant force
Of balance on a Saturday
Of balance…
Usually, we feel happy
when kids listen to their parents.
But my son has taken his
mom's word so seriously.
Sometimes, I don't know
whether to laugh or cry about it.
Is he still doing the Saturday thing?
He's not just following it.
Like a lizard that grows into a chameleon,
he's obsessed with the concept.
From Sunday to Friday,
he comes home without picking
a fight no matter how pissed he is.
But before going to bed,
he writes in his diary
as if it's holy scripture.
"Who?"
"What they have done?"
He follows this religiously till Friday.
-What about Saturday?
-Saturday!
He wakes up in the morning.
He introspects if he's still
angry at the people in his diary.
If his anger has passed, it's all good.
He strikes off their names.
And if he's still angry?
He circles their names.
NARAYANA PRABHA
And once he circles a name…
he goes to any length to beat them up.
He gets there one way or the other.
Hello, bro. My boss is going out of town.
He won't be back for another week.
Hello? Are you there, bro?
Hello?
You must've heard about
Yama and Chitragupta.
Imagine if he's both,
a split personality.
Where is he headed, looking like that?
It's normal to get angry
when our family is bothered.
But my son makes people his family,
based on his anger.
What do you mean?
Fazil, did he hit you again?
Yeah, bro.
-How many stitches did you get?
-Six.
Fazil, didn't I warn you about that man?
That stupid habit
of yours has led to this.
-But you couldn't care less.
-Cut him some slack.
That man roughed him up so
badly and you're taking his side.
Just be careful, man.
Everyone shows sympathy.
But nobody comes
forward to confront my boss.
Who's your boss?
Who are you, bro?
I'll tell you.
But first, who's your boss?
Aren't you coming back, Kali uncle?
Not if you keep crying like this.
Stop crying and study well.
I'll visit you soon.
-Don't get intimidated by Grandpa.
-Okay.
Call me if you need anything at all.
You can also
call me if you need anything.
What's up, Fazil?
Hello, sir. I'm Surya.
Are you expecting me to introduce myself?
Not at all. Who doesn't
know Narayana Prabha?
He told me you hit him because
he set the clock ten minutes ahead.
He could've lost his eye.
What do you propose we do?
Simple, sir.
Every action has a reason.
I think it was unfair to hit him
without knowing the reason.
If you listen to his reason…
you'll see why he did it.
-Bro…
-Tell him.
Speak out.
Well, sir…
My dad fell under
a running train and died.
Ever since then,
my mom would always say…
"I wish your father was ten
minutes early to the station.
Our lives would've been different."
That is why every time I see a clock,
I feel like setting it ten minutes ahead.
-I don't want anyone else to lose--
-You heard him.
Let's not get into whether
his habit is right or wrong.
But if his habit comes
from a good intention,
we should support him.
What do you have to say?
I have nothing to say.
-How is he related to you though?
-We're not related, sir.
No relation whatsoever.
But after listening to his story…
I got angry.
And once I get angry…
he becomes my family.
His problem becomes mine.
He won't work for you if
you're going to hit him again.
Promise me you won't.
I'll apologize to the kid first…
and then deal with your anger.
No apologies needed, sir.
-Sir!
-You expect me to apologize,
you little scum!
Was that a warning?
"There was a demon called
Narakasur in the olden days.
He used to trouble people a lot.
I arrived ten minutes early to a
meeting and everyone called me jobless.
You didn't just do a shitty job…
but you gave me
an even shittier reason.
Don't even get me started on this bugger.
What are you chanting in Hindi?
What are you going to do?
Hey!
If you don't quit that habit of yours…
I'll whack you again.
And this time, I'll make
sure you lose your eye.
You'll lose an eye as well,
for taking his side.
You understand?
Get lost!
Hey, get him stitched up again
and send him back to work.
Who the hell are you, bro?
You dragged me all the way for this?
Just like you…
I have a habit as well.
I didn't know he could fight, man.
In your eyes, in front of you
He'll show fear!
Not one, not two
In the list of eight, he's burst out!
All in all, the one playing
Is like a butterfly!
Even if he's caught, he won't show
He keeps it in his mound!
Guys, the angry bird came
with a half-shaved face.
Shave the rest and send him home.
On the enemy's head slate
He writes fate!
Fist by fist, it's Yama
If you smile, it's Shiva
Heart by heart, it's iron
Body of an elephant
Whoever the enemy
If he comes, he bleeds
Face of fire and water
He's a different breed
Fazil won't work for you anymore.
Thanks, bro.
Goodbye, sir.
Goodbye.
Get this stitched up.
Hey, I don't understand.
Why didn't you hit me that day?
And why did you hit me today?
What? Did I hit a nerve?
Everyone has seven days in a week.
But I have only one.
Only one day.
Saturday.
Why?
Isn't that enough?
As Brahma, as Narasimha
He'll create a new world, watch!
As Buddha, as a great warrior
Will transform into a fierce tiger
To touch or to leave
He'll say instantly, that person
On Saturday he'll fight the enemy
On other days, like a sage!
So, your son is rowdy?
Hey, not at all.
Then?
Mention that his leg
was broken as well, sir.
It will help them when they're on a break.
-Why don't you do it?
-No, sir. It's your job.
You always have some shit to say.
To wish for your family's wellness
for as long as you live is selfishness.
But to wish for your family's
wellness even while you're gone is…
responsibility.
This is our life insurance.
That is Surya!
Since our 25th anniversary is coming up…
I'm giving Surya the responsibility
of picking the Chief Guest.
Claps, guys.
When a guy with such a
peculiar lifestyle lives in the house…
imagine how peculiar
our lifestyle must be.
Hey!
There was a demon--
-I'm Santhosh.
-He's here, brother.
Bhadra, we have to go.
What's wrong, Surya?
-Let's go.
-Surya!
-Just get on the damn bike.
Leave the car behind.
Come fast. Run.
Hey, get back here!
Hey!
There lived a demon called
Narsapur in the olden days.
It's not Narsapur.
It's Narakasur.
There lived a demon!
Why did he spare him?
The clock struck 12.
-So he won't hit him till next Saturday?
-No.
He'll never hit him again.
There's another stupid
rule in his rulebook.
If he can't hit a certain
person by that Saturday,
he believes his mom
doesn't want him to hit them.
So he spares them
forever in his mom's name.
He even made friends out of this.
Hey!
Thank you for sparing my grandpa.
Happy New Year.
I thought at least marriage would fix him.
Hey, there was this girl, right?
What's her name?
Kallu. Did you guys find her?
We moved multiple times due to this guy.
So we completely lost touch.
Bu,t he…
-Your name?
-Kalyani.
Is your mom's name Prabhavathi?
Which Prabhavathi?
Who the hell are you,
calling at this hour?
Nothing. No. No. We're calling
from the Election Commission.
We don't know where they live now.
Even if we do, she hates you.
She wouldn't even step inside
the house when you were around.
That was back then.
I'm a changed man. She'll
also change when she finds out.
This is not the film Mayabazar where
everyone changes instantaneously.
Moreover, it's not enough if
you declare that you've changed.
What if she's married by now?
-Exactly!
-Hey!
Why do you manifest negative things?
Y'all may not know how much I love her.
But my aunt knows.
She would never let her get married.
I expected this.
He has a fixated mindset.
Once he sets his mind
to something, that's it.
That is why we did what we had to.
They say remove a thorn with a thorn.
But what about Kallu?
It's been four years
since Mom left us, Surya.
She remembered you even in her last days.
That's true.
Apparently, they searched for us
to invite us to her wedding.
But we moved so much, you know.
We're living in Mumbai now, Surya.
My husband got a job in the US recently.
We came to Hyderabad
for some visa work.
I was at the bank…
when I heard a sweet
voice say "Uncle" from behind.
Initially, I was surprised
to see who it was.
I couldn't believe that
Kallu was all grown up now.
This is my husband, Surya.
He's your brother by relation.
He belongs in the 60s or 70s.
He's so old fashioned, I forget
who's the father and who's the son.
Surya!
Surya, don't cry.
Listen to me.
-What's this?
-It's a ring.
When did you buy it?
First salary.
-How much was it?
-Go away!
It's okay, Surya.
Oh, my dear.
Why are you crying?
I can see you and your mom are happy.
Oh, no! Poor boy!
He's not so noble that
you feel sympathy for him.
You wouldn't say that if you heard
what he did at his sister's wedding.
There was a disagreement
regarding the bride's saree.
Bhadra wanted to wear her mom's saree.
We need to compromise
on a few things in a love marriage.
They wanted her to wear the saree
that was offered to the Goddess.
Don't you think
we have our own sentiments?
My daughter's stubbornness won in the end.
Before things calmed down,
something ugly was said.
-Don't get on my nerves.
-Listen to me, brother.
Should we back down because
of a random floozy who's no more?
-To hell with you guys!
-Somebody might hear you.
I don't care. I'm not afraid.
He shouldn't have said that.
I'm equally pissed.
I'll handle him. I'll go talk to him.
Hey! Stop with the mumbling.
Listen.
If you do anything right now,
she's going to pay for it later on.
Keep that in mind.
We assumed we had convinced him.
But we could only control him
till the wedding was over…
That's what we realized
once the clock struck 12.
Surya, stop!
Listen to me.
-Surya, I said stop!
-How dare you hit me!
Don't you have respect for the elders?
I'm going to teach you a lesson.
I'm the groom's father,
for heaven's sake.
-Are you out of your mind, Surya?
-Hit him.
Please stop, Surya. I'm begging you.
Surya!
We discussed this before
going ahead with the marriage.
Look at him.
Why does Dad have to
beg them for forgiveness?
Can't you see his pain?
How can I live with
that family after this?
Imagine how they'll treat me.
So, you don't really care about us.
You just want to
get your way all the time.
I've had enough.
I'm so fed up of trying
to change your ways.
Do whatever the hell you want!
I won't be a part of your life anymore.
And I expect the same from you.
Sister…
Please don't say that.
Sorry.
-I'll go apologize to them as well.
-No need.
Just let me go.
I said let go!
Surya, you know me.
I'll do something regretful
if you don't let me go.
She's my only daughter.
I couldn't even give her
a proper send-off.
My son-in-law is a good man.
He stood by her.
Because of this foolish man,
she doesn't have a maternal
or a paternal home now.
Imagine how I must be feeling.
I'd be fuming with rage.
That is why I went out of my way
and decided something.
Every Saturday,
I made it my duty to find his targets
at any cost and save them.
He doesn't hit them once
that Saturday passes.
In fact, that is why I came to see you.
I'm sorry, I don't get it.
The second name on my son's list
for this Saturday is…
Teertham Gunasekhar.
That's your husband, right?
He's not in the city.
He said he'd be back in two days
since he had a fever.
You have a temperature of 102 degrees.
Drink this.
Go to sleep.
Now!
I don't know what your husband has done.
He works at the same
school as my daughter.
Are you okay?
Hey, Bhadra ma'am. Just a minute.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
If you report this and the news gets out,
she will suffer the
consequences more than me.
See you.
Damn…
Time to wake up.
THE TURN
YOUR SAFETY IS OUR PRIORITY
Sir.
New joinee.
Charulatha.
-Joining today?
-Yes, sir.
Show this to the CI once he's here.
Take this.
-Sir, the CI…
-He will be coming.
Eat your food.
Waiting for the CI, right?
I see that you're eager to join duty.
This is how it is at first.
But once you meet him,
you'll never ask to see him again.
That's how our CI is.
Dayanand.
-Sudha…
-Sir.
The car is stinking despite
trying so many perfumes.
Yes, sir.
-We should find a new perfume.
-Sir.
Do you know any?
Good perfumes.
-Did you send his video?
-Sir?
-Did you send his video or not?
-Yes, I did, sir.
I called him as well.
But no response.
I wonder what's keeping him so busy.
What the hell is he up to?
Speak up.
Who the hell sent you?
-I didn't stab him.
-Who sent you?
-I'm telling the truth.
-Spit it out.
I said, speak out!
Who the hell sent you, damn it?
-I really don't know anything.
-Who sent you, man?
-Do you want to tell us or die?
-Believe me, bro.
-You bloody bugger! Tell us!
-Hey, stop!
Stop it! Cut the drama!
Just stop!
Why did you want to kill me?
-Has the video downloaded?
-Network is slow here, bro.
Go outside and do it.
-What are you standing here for? Get out.
-Okay.
Do you know how it feels
to have a threat to your life?
It wasn't me, sir.
You can't sleep, relax,
or, do anything at all, in fact.
You're always looking out
for an attack on you.
Your heart keeps pounding
in your ears out of fear.
You can't focus on anything else.
You go crazy.
Just like I am right now.
Tell me.
Why did you stab me at the airport?
-Tell me!
-Sir, I swear I'm innocent.
Some other guy was trying to stab you.
I intervened to stop him.
Do I look like a fool to you?
Am I looking like a fricking fool?
-I really don't know, sir.
-Okay, no problem.
-Are you going to spit it out now?
-Brother!
-I'm really innocent, sir.
-Yeah, right. You're a good boy.
Bro, he's right.
Hey, quiet!
He's not the one who attempted murder.
He just grabbed the knife from him.
In fact, he's the one who saved you.
Couldn't you come a bit early, you moron?
He has lost half a liter of blood already.
And a finger.
Bro, bro, bro… I'm sorry.
Please don't mind.
I have a judgment issue due to this eye.
I can't see things clearly.
Hence the lapse in judgment.
What are you guys looking at?
Rush him to the hospital.
Go, go, go.
Don't worry.
Why is my judgment
so off all the time, man?
Wrong judgment every fricking time!
Where's Govardhan?
Please, sir.
I have two kids.
Oh, two kids!
A girl and a boy?
Both boys.
Wow, two boys!
You must have been elated.
Who's your favorite?
The elder one or the younger one?
Nothing like that, sir.
I love them equally.
If you give me such soap opera bullshit,
I'll put a bullet in your head.
Be honest.
The elder one or the younger one?
I love my younger one a little more, sir.
I knew it.
Because you became the father
of two sons after he was born.
Am I right?
I guess so, sir.
Hey, idiot!
You became a father in the first
place because of the elder son.
By that logic, he should be your favorite.
You don't get it.
You think nobody knows that you
love your younger son a little more.
But your elder son
is watching from a corner.
He's furious on the inside.
But on who?
Me.
No, you idiot.
Why would he be furious at you?
He's furious at your younger son.
If all this anger builds up…
And say, you die tomorrow,
what if the elder one betrays his younger
brother while splitting the assets?
What will you do?
With the wealth inherited from you
and the wealth looted
from his younger brother,
your elder son will own
three times the money.
He will go on to become
a Corporator and then an MLA.
But your younger son
will be working a modest CI job,
with a salary that does him no good,
and a hopeless ambition to grow
as big as his elder brother.
In an attempt to save the only
piece of land he owns now,
he kidnaps his brother's
auditor and Benami,
assuming that he's a very important man.
Only to find out that
he's a loser like you.
Now the elder son
doesn't answer his calls.
See?
Your favoritism led to so many troubles.
Such a waste!
-Sudha.
-Sir.
Let him go.
But why, sir?
What else can we do, Sudha?
He's a waste piece.
Like tissue paper.
If he were so important…
my brother would've
called immediately and said,
"If you hurt Govardhan,
I'll not spare you.
You want my signature
on the land papers, right?
You can have it. Send the papers over."
That's what would've happened.
Tissue paper.
Let him go.
Hello! Hey, hey!
Let Govardhan go!
I'll not spare you if you hurt him.
You want my signature, right?
Send the papers over.
But if you don't let him go
as soon as I sign the papers…
Hey! Hey!
Sudha! Sudha!
-Catch him! He's highly important!
-What's wrong, sir?
-Govardhan!
-He left, sir.
He's not a waste piece, Sudha.
I'm the loser here.
What happened, sir?
-My brother called.
-Sir?!
I have to do something.
I let the opportunity slip.
I just let 45 crores go.
-I have to do something.
-Should I start the car?
SOKULAPALEM
I don't think he's coming today.
Listen to me, go home.
Hey!
-Hey!
-Sir…
I guess you just got lucky.
There he is.
Sir, I'm begging you!
Please let me go!
Hey!
Sir, I'm begging you!
Please let me go!
What did he do to deserve
such a brash beating, sir?
Have you heard of the famous Stuartpuram?
Similarly, here we have Sokulapalem.
Being born there is their biggest mistake.
Some people vent their anger
on their wives and kids.
Some people vent it on things.
Poor guy!
He doesn't have a wife or kids.
And the only things in hand are…
the people of Sokulapalem.
Hey!
Chinnu…
Do you know what true anger means?
Dad… Dad…
What is it?
Is it the true anger dream again?
What do you think Mom tried to tell me?
To heck with you, man!
You're giving me hell.
Hand me that book.
I noted this down from a sermon
by Nithyananda.
He says…
"Truth is anger.
And the anger is truth.
But the actual anger
resides in actual truth…
which in turn will become anger,
which is full of truth."
-It's definitely not that.
-What is it then?
You dozed off without listening to your
Mom completely when you were young.
Now you're not letting me sleep in peace.
I can't do this anymore.
Only a miracle worker can
save you from this tragedy.
What's the delay, man?
He said he's here, sir.
I don't know where he went.
I'll go check.
Sir, we'll be right back.
Sir…
-Sir!
-You dare ask me!
-Sir…
-What happened, sir?
How dare he ask me for
directions to the toilet, Sudha?
Do I look jobless enough to give
you directions to the toilet?
I thought you were
a friendly police officer, sir.
-Find the toilets by yourself.
-Okay, sir.
Can't you do the bare minimum
to clear your bladder?
-What happened, Sudha?
-Sir, he spoke to your brother.
Despite telling him that you let
Govardhan go before his call came,
he's creating a fuss
about the whole thing.
Clients are waiting upstairs.
They agreed to wait only for a month.
Why is your daughter going
to Bangalore all of a sudden?
Bangalore? She hasn't told me about it.
You're getting a call.
Hello, dear.
Dad, I'm going to Bangalore for a meeting.
That's sudden.
Yeah, I know.
They informed me last minute.
I have to leave early in the morning.
I have a lot of packing to do. Bye, Dad.
Alright.
Take care.
How's my network?
It's like washing your face
after bawling your eyes out.
Stop giving money to the peon
until she comes back at least.
By the way,
Mr. Chakravarthy wants you to know
that his daughter lives here.
Isn't it kind of unsafe
to reveal her whereabouts?
Enough of your lame jokes.
What should I tell them?
Hey!
Is this it, Dad?
Don't you think Kallu
and her husband would fight maybe?
Why? Do you plan on getting her
divorced and then marrying her?
Apparently, they're planning
for a second child.
She doesn't even take my calls anymore.
-That's how busy he keeps her.
-Enough!
If my aunt were alive…
she wouldn't have agreed to this.
If only she were alive.
Don't shush me.
Your aunt helped us a great deal.
We need to have some gratitude.
We changed our real names
for fear of alerting your father.
We dug our own graves in a way.
Otherwise, you would've
been married to him by now.
Hello, Subhashini alias Prabhavathi.
We can show a lifetime
of gratitude for her help.
But no stupid theories about
marrying Chinnu, please.
You can't just assume
that he's still as aggressive.
Who knows?
Maybe he's a changed man now.
He'll never change.
You know it.
Water, please.
Water, sir.
-No, no.
-Have it.
-Open the cell.
-Okay, sir.
New joinee, sir.
New joinee.
Okay, sir.
Charulatha.
I guess you have a helping nature.
I love the perfume.
-Which brand is it?
-Sir?
Which perfume do you use?
I don't use perfume, sir.
What am I smelling then?
Is it body odor?
-Sudha…
-Sir.
Stop laughing.
I just found a new perfume for our car.
Talk to her.
-Hey!
-Sir! Sir! No!
I warned you against this.
We're not allowed to offer him
anything without the CI's permission.
But you didn't listen.
That man reminded me of my mom, sir.
My dad used to beat up
my mom daily for no reason.
We would wait in hope every day
to get out of that hell hole.
To be honest,
that's why I took up this job.
In the hope of doing my best
to help other women like my mom.
If so, you should help
everyone in that village.
Sokulapalem.
It used to be a criminal hub.
It's a crime-free region now.
They've swayed away
from crimes long ago.
But they're still paying the cost
for their ancestors' mistakes.
They can't find work anywhere.
Even if they want to get
a new job somewhere else…
or earn a livelihood here…
they need the CI's stamp of approval.
What's the problem, sir?
A few years ago, our CI's land
ended up in a court litigation.
Guess who filed the case.
It was his elder brother, Kurmanand.
Our CI was unlucky.
Kurmanand became the Corporator with
the support of the people of Sokulapalem.
He used that influence
to win the court case.
The verdict said
that our CI couldn't access
that land without his brother's signature.
He didn't do any good
to the people as a Corporator.
But our CI blamed the people
for putting him in this position.
He developed deep anger
for the people of Sokulapalem.
He couldn't get back at his brother
since he's politically powerful now.
Hence, every time he's angry with him,
he goes to Sokulapalem.
He picks one of them.
He arrests them.
He files odd cases on them.
He hits them.
He keeps hitting them.
Hey!
Has nobody ever complained against him?
A complaint?
Against him?
Against our Daya?
Look at that.
She waits there every day.
Has she stepped into the station once
and questioned him?
She won't.
It's fear.
They just hope that he cuts back
on the beating after seeing them.
That's their only battle.
SOKULAPALEM
Where does Raju live?
Thanks.
-Mom…
-Is your mom home?
Mom…
Raju hasn't eaten in five days.
-I know, ma'am.
-Then pack lunch quickly.
I have to go.
-Namaste, ma'am.
-Namaste.
-What do you do?
-I'm a carpenter, ma'am.
I run that chicken shop, ma'am.
Don't worry, I've got this.
Bye.
Should I be happy that
he got to eat today?
Or should I be sad wondering how long
this will persist? I don't know.
None of us expected this hint
of positivity, right?
Look at this.
I hurt myself.
They say this is karma
for your past mistakes.
If this is the level of pain we're
subjected to for our petty mistakes…
imagine the kind of hammering that monster
is going to receive for torturing us.
Charu…
Get in. Charu, let's go.
-Did you hurt yourself at the shoot?
-Yes, sir.
Sir.
Here.
Sorry.
Sorry? Don't you have common sense?
-What did you say?
-I said don't you have common sense?
-You're supposed to be careful.
-I apologized, right?
Is an apology sufficient?
What if something happened?
-Sudha, go stand there.
-Sir.
-Sir, don't. We're at a hospital.
-Stand behind the car. Go, go, go.
-Charu, come.
-Sir.
Stand in the center.
If the car moves…
I'll kill you both.
What if something happened?
Sir!
There was a demon called
Narakasur in the olden days.
He used to trouble people a lot.
Sir, stop!
Who the hell are you?
An explosion waiting to happen.
Your car, sir. Petrol is leaking.
What if it catches fire
from all the thudding?
You'll be dead.
Dead beyond recognition.
-Check it.
-Sir.
Yes, sir. There's a leak.
Aunty…
I do have common sense.
Hi.
Your bottle cap.
It's not mine.
I saw what you did.
Thanks for saving that lady.
I'm Charulatha.
Surya.
Hello, ma'am?
I see that your bike ran out of fuel.
Come, I'll take you to the petrol pump.
Oh, no. It's okay.
I know it's okay.
That's why I offered to help.
Do you have a bottle to carry the petrol?
No.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
I guess my bike ran out of fuel now.
-I do have common sense.
-Sir!
Aunty…
-Dad!
-What is it now?
The "true anger" dream?
I watched a white guy's sermon just now.
I'll explain everything after this show.
No, wait. Let me watch.
-It's not that, Dad.
-Damn.
-Two things happened today.
-What are those?
-I got angry at a guy.
-It's common.
And I met a girl.
I met her and came back home.
I sat down to write his name
but I can't stop thinking about her.
I'm not able to pen down the name.
I can't seem to understand why.
Who's this girl?
Her name is Charulatha.
Charu…
Her name starts with "Cha"
just like Mom's.
Chayadevi. Charulatha.
Do you think that's the connection?
We have a neighbor
called Chamundeshwari.
Did you ever look at her
and feel this way?
See? It's not in the name.
Listen to me.
If there's an emotion beyond your anger…
what could it be?
What could it be?
What's happening to me?
These are joys I'm not used to
Something has nestled in my heart
My emotions change
My anger is calmed when I'm with you
Your intoxication lightens my heart
The heart is unlike yesterday
It doesn't respond to me when I ask why
A bubbling heart
And excitement in my breath
I'm drenched in
Showers of your thoughts
This connection is destined to be
Whispers of silence
Words slip away from the lips
Our imagination touches the skies
Where are we headed?
What's happening to me?
These are joys I'm not used to
He has the same name as your nephew.
But he's nothing like your Chinnu.
Every time I look at Charu,
she reminds me so much of Kallu.
Her smile, the way she talks, all of it.
I didn't have this feeling
when I met the real Kallu, Dad.
Simple.
We tend to see our loved ones
in the people we love.
Kallu is married now.
So, you're thinking of the young Kallu
every time you see Charu.
-Do you think he found the real Kallu?
-I don't think so.
It feels like I'm cloaked by your thoughts
When you smile with all your heart
New light enters my eyes
Sokulapalem is a thieves' den, right?
I don't have any proof to prove otherwise.
But they really need this insurance.
Please do it for me, Surya.
The threads of our hands are intertwined
Strengthened by fate
We will not be separated
But will move forward as a pair
A bubbling heart
And excitement in my breath
I'm drenched in
Showers of your thoughts
This connection is destined to be
Girlfriend?
I liked my aunt's daughter
when I was young.
-But she's married now.
-Oh.
What about you?
The guy I'm going to marry shouldn't
even know the spelling of violence.
Where can I find one these days?
Oh, this is where you live.
Please don't mind me not inviting you in.
Mom might have a problem.
Hey, it's totally alright.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah, it's okay.
-Bye.
Charu…
So, does the alphabet "S"
appear once or twice in the word violence?
Lense… There must be an S.
-Bye.
-No, I really don't know.
Is it a single S or double S?
Hey, she's growing fond of you
because of those six days.
God forbid she finds out
about your seventh day.
How will she find out?
I got discharged yesterday, man.
Sorry, ma'am.
Forgive us for our mistake, ma'am.
Hello.
Look at this.
Swamy, the bakery guy, and my SI.
He hit all of them on a Saturday.
Which means,
he hits people only on Saturdays.
You're acting like Prakash Raj
from the film Tagore.
You solved 90 percent of the case.
Is that a joke?
You don't get it.
He's observing me closely.
I'm worried about what
he might do in the future.
Do you think that's him?
-Who?
-The Saturday guy.
You're overthinking this.
He's not so cool.
Forget about him.
How can I just let it go?
How do I explain it to you?
Okay.
Take the movie Eega for example.
Nani loves Samantha.
Samantha loves Nani as well.
But before she can express her love…
Kiccha Sudeep kills Nani.
Nani was reborn as a fly
because it's a movie.
-But what do we do in real life?
-Yeah, not possible.
I have a feeling that this guy
is like Kiccha Sudeep.
You get it?
Are you saying the
Saturday guy is Kiccha Sudeep?
Yeah.
-Samantha?
-That's me.
Who's Nani?
Are you crazy? You are Nani.
-Me?
-A bubbling heart
And excitement in my breath
I'm drenched in
Showers of your thoughts
This connection is destined to be
Whispers of silence
Words slip away from the lips
Our imagination touches the skies
Dad, she's calling.
I'll be talking to her.
You keep saying, "Nani, come here.
Nani, do this, etc."
-Nani? Who's that?
-It's me!
Hello, I'm just at home.
-Nani!
-Yes, Dad?
Come and do the dishes.
-The food is delicious?
-No, come do the dishes.
Yeah, coming.
THE KNOT
-Don't turn right. Turn left.
-That road is bad.
-I said turn left.
-Got it, brother.
I agree what Daya did in my case is wrong.
But he let me go before
your call came that day.
Trust me on this once.
Do we need this drama hanging over us?
Sir, he's your little brother after all.
He's been asking you for a long time now.
Why don't you meet him
and sign the papers?
-What's wrong?
-The road is blocked.
Why is my judgment so off every time?
Always the wrong judgment!
But first, sir…
What do we do now?
-What?
-What do we do now?
-Open the cell.
-Yes, sir.
-Sir, sir…
-Hey! It's sharp. Get back.
-Be careful, man. Don't be scared.
-Sir.
Raju…
Do you want to go home?
Go.
-Sudha, release him.
-Sir.
How come, sir?
My brother is giving me my land back.
He's going to sign the agreement
once he's back in the city.
I don't need this guy anymore.
Dude, go.
Be happy.
Go, go, go.
Go tell everyone to be happy.
The agreement will be signed
on the coming Saturday.
I'll get my land back.
Take it off!
Bro, he has a girlfriend.
I'm glad.
Should we get them both married?
Brother, she doesn't know
about his Saturday concept.
That means…
he won't lift a finger in her
presence even on a Saturday.
If he does, he'll get
into trouble with her.
If he doesn't,
he'll get into trouble with us.
Fantastic!
The time has come to hit
him on a Saturday, Martin!
Go!
Take our whole gang.
Let's check out his eternal love story.
-Hey!
-Brother…
I'm getting some surgery done tomorrow.
I want to hear good news before that.
Go, go.
Mom, I'm off to work.
What does he like to eat?
Shall I invite him over?
Now that she's told her mom about you,
I think it's unfair to
hide the truth from her.
True. Let's say before you confess,
she finds out that you're
both Nani and Kiccha Sudeep,
the movie won't be called
Eega anymore.
It'd be called Gabbilam.
I'm afraid about how she'll react, Dad.
Hey…
If you confess,
you'll be telling the truth.
But if she finds out…
you'll be cheating her.
Think about it.
-All hail…
-Mr. Kurmanand!
Sir, Mr. Daya is here.
What did he call you? Tissue paper?
Let that go, brother.
Just sign the land papers
and be done with it.
That… I…
Sir.
Go and ask if he would
like to have coffee or tea.
Okay, sir.
-Did you get it?
-Sir?
Ask him.
-Don't serve anything. Go.
-Okay, sir.
Sir, would you like to have coffee or tea?
Sir, shall I order coffee?
-One coffee and one tea.
-Okay, sir.
-And one water bottle.
Why do you sound so serious and formal?
-What is this about?
-I'll tell you when we meet.
You're going to meet Mom
and me in the evening anyway.
Yeah, I want to meet you once before that.
Okay.
Sir, coffee or tea?
Hey, we ordered half an hour ago.
-Sorry, sir. I totally forgot.
-What?
-One coffee, one tea, and a water bottle.
-Okay, sir.
Also, tell him that Daya sir is waiting.
-Yes.
Sir, would you like to have coffee or tea?
Are you guys kidding me?
How many times do we…
One coffee.
One tea.
And a water bottle if you may.
-Hello.
-Who's next?
-Bro, I'm sending Kumar in.
-Go ahead.
Sir, would you like to have coffee or tea?
Choose your words wisely.
-Is that him? Let's go!
-Hurry up! Go, go, go!
I'm sure it was deliberate.
We made a huge mistake
by letting Govardhan go that day.
Otherwise…
Let's go.
Get inside! Go! Go!
Please don't hit me, sir.
Please, don't hit me.
-What's the update?
-She's not here yet.
You should attack him
only in her presence.
Otherwise, he'll wreak havoc on you guys.
Alright.
You dare to have his picture?
-Do you think so highly of him?
-Sir, no!
Sir, please don't hit him. He'll die!
Sir, please stop! Sir!
-Sir, please stop!
-Mom!
-Sir, let me go.
-Sir, please let go of my dad.
Sir, let her go!
Lalli!
I think the little girl is hurt.
Hey!
I'll kill you if you move forward.
He invited me home on the premise
of giving my land back…
Lalli!
and went on to humiliate me further.
How could you paint such a man's picture?
Hello, where are you? It's been a while.
-Why did you paint his picture?
-Lalitha…
If I hear his name again,
-I'll turn Sokulapalem into a graveyard.
-Lalitha.
Trust me!
Oh, dear!
Dear!
Brother, somebody, help!
He left.
Somebody, help!
Somebody, please come forward.
My girl is going to die.
Lalli…
Lalli!
How is she doing?
They're checking.
It's high time that you file a complaint.
I'm talking to you.
File a complaint and kill her
chances of survival completely?
I don't want that.
We're used to this misery.
How can you say that?
If you file a complaint, this
won't happen to someone else.
If only the people before
us took some action,
we wouldn't be subjected
to this suffering now.
Why should we worry about someone else?
We're all united in fear.
Not in fighting that demon.
Where is your CI right now?
What will you do about it, Surya?
This isn't as easy as saving
that woman by spilling petrol.
All we can do is listen,
watch, and sit in agony.
We're hopeless.
Today is a Saturday.
You know what I feel right now?
If that Saturday guy were here…
right now, standing in front of me…
I would want to ask him for a favor.
Ask.
I told you he won't lift a finger
in her presence even on a Saturday.
He, the one who breaks
The shackles of doubt
With a fierce and intense gaze
His nails are like blazing
Flames on a mountain
He is the constant force
Of balance on a Saturday
Ask.
This is a fight between you and me.
Why did you guys touch her?
I can express anger only one day a week.
My mom took this promise from me.
That's the deal with Saturday.
Only on a Saturday.
I don't know what favor you wanted to ask.
But I got angry.
And because I'm angry,
this problem just became my problem.
Sokulapalem is my family now.
I have to go to work in the morning.
We don't have an off day.
You don't work on Sundays, right?
I guess so.
I hope the girl will be fine.
What did you say his name was?
Oh.
Daya.
SOKULAPALEM
There lived a demon called
Narakasur in the olden days.
Come, come!
He used to trouble people a lot.
So Sri Krishna and
Satyabhama teamed up and…
killed him!
The sound of crackling
It's like the roaring of the sky
Here's to the fall of the mighty ones
The blazing ground is scorched
The battle that cannot be unseen
Blood has already begun to boil
The war has tipped the balance
Destruction is inevitable
You've played a big game.
The war has tipped the balance
Destruction is inevitable
You've played a big game.
CROSSROADS
Bhadru, how are your sugar levels?
You're in your ninth month.
Tell your family at least now.
Did you eat?
How long will you keep avoiding this?
Don't act so stubborn.
You lied about going to Bangalore
and stayed back in the same city.
What's the need to live at
your friend's place like this?
I'm not with you during a time like this.
I feel guilty
to leave you all by yourself.
Think about it.
Hey…
Did you tell her?
Yeah.
What did she say?
She left without saying a word.
She left?
Did you tell her properly or not?
I didn't just tell her.
I showed her.
What do you mean?
I don't know what to do, Mom.
He's the kind of guy
I didn't want in my life.
But I fell in love with the same guy.
Even though I know the truth,
I don't feel like losing him.
Is it the situation…
or is it my love for him?
I just don't understand.
SUNDAY
Thanks for understanding.
What do you plan on doing this Saturday?
So you're going to hit the CI, right?
You said the people of Sokulapalem
are family, and this is your problem now.
Hitting him may calm your anger.
But that doesn't mean
their problem will be solved.
I don't know if I can say this
to someone who helped us.
Never help us again.
If something happens to you going forward,
that will affect us only.
Look what happened to that girl.
Did anyone come forward to help?
I'm one to speak.
Did I come forward to help?
We've gotten used to the fear.
We'll never change.
This is it.
Our lives are doomed.
MONDAY
I don't know what happened there.
But it's highly impossible to go
ahead without your brother's signature.
The clients are adamant.
They want to buy the land before
Sunday or move on to another seller.
It's not going to work
out with Kurmanand, sir.
If you were there, you'd never
have coffee or tea again in your life.
What do we do then?
Sir, as long as your brother's here,
we need his signature.
What if he isn't?
What if my brother is no more?
What are you talking about, sir?
-It's Kurmanand, sir.
-To hell with him!
You'll get the news
before the coming Sunday.
Before the coming Sunday.
Daya is planning to kill his brother.
We just have to make sure
Kurmanand finds out about this.
Then Kurmanand will deal with Daya.
Do you think that's going to solve
Sokulapalem's problem?
Dayanand is their only problem.
Daya isn't the only problem.
It's the fear that's rooted in them.
Let's say Daya is gone.
Tomorrow, some other
evil guy will take over.
The fear will come back.
That fear should disappear.
And for that to happen,
they need a ray of hope in their lives.
But how?
Even if one guy from Sokulapalem
steps forward with courage…
all their lives will change.
Courage from the people of Sokulapalem?
It doesn't have to be one of them.
They just need to believe
that one of them already did.
Isn't that enough?
TUESDAY
Who is this guy?
"My patience has worn out.
My tears have dried out.
On behalf of all of us,
I want to overcome the fear
and take a step forward.
I'll take the first step this Saturday.
One of us."
Who is this guy?
Who could it be?
One of us?
It's not me, bro.
What could the first step be?
And why Saturday?
Who could it be?
He said he'll take the first step.
Maybe he'll massage his feet
for these four days.
Am I right, sir?
Am I right, ma'am?
Have some shame!
Don't you see our pain in those words?
Keep watching.
This Saturday…
our lives are going to change.
Because of one of us.
There are only two common spots
in Kurmanand's routine, sir.
He goes to the temple at 10:00 a.m.
He goes to the pub at 11:00 p.m.
But more people escort him
to the pub than the temple.
So security-wise,
the temple is a better spot.
Which temple does he go to?
A different temple every day,
depending on which day it is.
Shivalayam on Mondays,
Hanuman temple on Tuesdays,
Ayyappa temple on Wednesdays.
Sai Baba temple on Thursdays,
Gayatri temple on Fridays,
and on Saturdays…
Balaji temple.
WEDNESDAY
But the catch is he's flying
to Delhi Thursday night.
He won't be back until next Wednesday.
Sir, we told the clients that the
agreement will be done by Sunday.
If we postpone it, they'll
cancel the deal altogether.
What do we do, sir?
They're planning something at
the Sai Baba temple tomorrow.
We'll move the plan to Saturday.
But how?
Surya, my boy!
Sir, I found the Chief Guest
for our 25th anniversary.
You did?
Who's that?
25th Anniversary?
THURSDAY
-Nice card.
-I designed it, sir.
But I can't make it.
I'm going to Delhi.
Sir, he'll explain
the agenda in two minutes.
I'm going to the temple.
I'll see you in the evening.
-He's going to the temple.
-He's saying evening.
Sir!
You don't come.
But please listen to the
speech I prepared for you.
It's up to you to go to Delhi or not.
Once you hear the speech,
you'll never go to Delhi again.
Costly flowers, sir.
Ma'am, give me two rupees, please.
You're so beautiful.
Ma'am! God will bless you.
Hey!
Thank you, sir.
Why did you give 500 rupees, sir?
Our work gets done quickly when
we do such things once in a while.
Sir, the prayer is almost done.
I don't think he's coming.
Greetings, sir.
Go.
Go!
-Find out what happened.
-Sir.
-Nice.
-Thank you, sir.
What was that? It's selfish of me…
to wish for your wellness
when I'm in power.
FRIDAY
But it's my responsibility to wish for
your wellness even when I'm not in power.
He postponed his Delhi
trip to next Monday for this.
Our only option now is this Saturday.
Saturday.
If we miss him at the temple,
what can we do at the bar that night?
This is our only chance, Surya.
If we miss this…
We won't miss it!
I won't let it happen.
SATURDAY
Hey, Kali…
Your father was doing
well when you were here.
Some guy Surya…
He got me so worked up.
Don't spare him!
Inspector…
-Yes, uncle?
-Listen.
-Who's Inspector Daya?
-He's a psycho case. Why?
This madman has written down his name.
I don't know what to do.
Should I go tell Daya
that he's coming to hit him?
And ask him to be careful, maybe?
Will you warn a cop that
your son is going to hit him?
What do you want me to do then?
Uncle…
Dear…
drink this.
-Sudha.
-Sir, he's on the way.
Go, go.
Dear…
"Daya started!"
Dad…
Dad what?
Go back to sleep.
I told you to tell me when
someone messes with Dad.
So?
Who the hell is Surya?
Where's Surya?
-Where is he?
-Surya…
Come here. Come.
Why did you get a gang?
Shooting something?
Where's Surya?
What day is it today?
Saturday.
He doesn't come to work
even on my orders.
Do you think he'll show up for you?
What's that scar on the face?
We have a special policy for that.
Come.
Where's Surya?
I don't know.
Scoot the knife back a little.
I don't have an insurance policy.
-Yes?
-Narayana Prabha is dead.
His men are looking for Surya.
They shouldn't find him.
Hey!
He has fallen asleep.
-What do you want me to do?
-How can I tell you?
They'll be coming home. Do something.
Okay, hang up!
Him and his stupid ideas!
Surya… Surya…
Wake up!
Dad…
-Hey! You're supposed to watch the road!
-Sorry, sir.
Start the car!
Sir, he's at the temple.
Where are you?
Start the vehicle!
Sir, sir, sir…
I'm trying!
-Hey, auto! Stop, stop!
-Sir!
Take me to the Balaji temple.
I have to pick the school kids.
Who are you, sir?
Do as I say. Go!
Go fast!
Sir, he's leaving! Come fast!
I'm coming, Sudha! I'm coming!
I'm coming, Sudha!
Uncle, can you please move?
Hey! I'll punch you! Move!
Stop!
Bro, nobody knows.
Where else did you see him?
You should've come a little sooner.
The pub is our last hope.
But…
Our car is starting, sir.
You…
Get the keys.
Go!
Go! Go!
The pub is our last option, sir.
But it's difficult to get
through the security and go in.
You should be really
careful in the next two to three weeks.
Is none of your family here?
Think about it.
Forget about your brother.
At least tell your dad.
Do you understand me?
Someone said there's going to
be a miraculous change soon.
What happened?
Nobody here has the guts, Uncle.
Listen to me. Don't be delusional.
Saturday and change, my foot!
I guess he's here.
It's some woman.
Should we tell her the house is locked?
Why? Can't she see for herself?
-Hello.
-Hello, Dad. Where are you?
The front door is locked.
-Wait, are you here?
-Yeah.
What are you doing
here at this time?
What happened, Dad?
It's your brother's usual mess.
No, what happened?
-Is nobody outside?
-No.
-Enter from the back door.
-So you're inside?
Just come in. I'll explain later.
Okay, okay. I'm coming.
You're pregnant?
What is she doing in front of
a locked house for so long?
Why did you keep it from me
when it was him you fought with?
Why did you show up now?
You should've directly come with the baby.
Bangalore, Mattigadda,
were all lies, right?
-Dad…
-Don't talk to me!
You're no different from him.
-How did you come?
-In my car.
Bloody car! Where did you park it?
Outside.
Outside--
What happened, Dad?
Hey!
This guy is home!
Surya… Surya…
Surya, wake up!
Stop!
Surya…
Surya!
Do you know what true anger means?
Kill him, guys!
Chinnu…
Why didn't you tell me?
Am I a stranger to you now?
Hey!
Bhadra! What happened, dear?
Surya!
-Careful, dear.
-Come.
Come and get her.
My father fell under a running
train and passed away, sir.
That is why I like to set
every clock ten minutes ahead.
Hey!
We just have to let Kurma
know that Daya is trying to kill him.
Kurma will handle Daya.
Hey! Come, come.
Come!
He hit Daya!
One of us hit Daya, Uncle.
He wore a mask and hit him!
Missed by an inch!
My brother…
Your brother's men
would be looking for us, sir.
I'll find a hideout for us.
My brother tried to…
One of us hit him!
Somebody hit our CI?
Find him!
Say it, Dad.
Tell me that nothing happened.
You asked me why I kept
my pregnancy from you, right?
If I did, I wouldn't have
made it to the ninth month.
When a guy like him is in the
family, why would I tell you?
One last thing, Dad.
If you want me to live with you…
he should give up his Saturday fights.
I don't care if you think
of this as blackmail.
He said whether it's a baby boy or a girl,
it's Mom coming back to us.
Ask him if he can
do it for Mom at least.
Light that guides through the darkness
Awakening the dawn
With every step
Are you moving forward or just beginning?
It's just a caterpillar during origin
And then it transforms into a butterfly
Have the patience to grow wings
Why do I feel like he's
the one who hit Daya?
-What? Him?
-Yes.
Look properly!
You think so?
Look how he's squeezing the garments.
I have a feeling it's him who hit Daya.
It's strange, Uncle.
Whoever I see is giving me
the feeling that they hit Daya.
Namaste, Uncle.
You also look like that to me.
What lies in which path?
You and Dad should
take care of your sister.
What? Where are you going?
I need to go now to
come back to you, right?
Unknowingly, it is revealing something
Is it showing some destination?
Words that cannot be crossed
And mistakes that cannot be corrected
As you try to change that
The path changes
Fate gives it to you with companionship
A game played without being seen
-What now? Should I thank you?
-I didn't ask you to.
I won't thank you even if you ask.
Thanks.
I have the doctor's appointment tomorrow.
Can you take me?
A wave is less intimidating
When you dive deep
It's okay to listen to your heart
It doesn't make you small
Time is an illusion
Is it going to lead the way?
The silence within you
Fills a bundle of hope
A turn has come, oh a turn has come
Where will this turn lead?
HIDE AND SEEK
Why?
Why did you do it?
What have I done to you?
Was it for insulting you at
my house the other day?
Or for making you go in circles around
me for that piece of land? Why?
Why did you save me?
Tell me.
Did I ever treat you like my brother?
Never.
Why do you love this mad person so much?
What have I done?
You got yourself hurt.
Why?
We may have a lot of differences.
But you're my big brother.
Nobody can change that.
Sir, coffee, tea.
Sir.
Here…
-Water bottle, sir.
-Coffee--
Have it.
You see how much
my brother loves me, Govi?
I've known since day one.
He let me go that day
before you called him.
You've always misunderstood him.
Wrong judgment!
I kept you away
for so long because of it.
But this will never
happen again. I promise.
If he went to such lengths
to save you, why did he hide?
For me…
what's more important than
living with my brother…
is his being alive.
Your answer has nothing
to do with what I asked.
You all kept me and my brother
away for so long with this attitude.
You're so doubtful, you would've
mistaken me for the killer.
-Water.
-Bro, it's not like that.
Shut up, you rascal!
You and your bloody doubts!
You moron! Just shut your mouth!
You take it.
Take this house, the land,
everything. I don't want it.
Take it.
Brother…
What did you say?
Brother.
This is enough for a lifetime.
My brother saved me.
This is enough for me.
Hey! Don't cry!
I want one thing though.
The guy who's been trying to kill me.
The guy who hurt my
brother who came to save me.
Don't spare him!
I won't, brother!
I won't spare him, for your sake.
How is…
everyone?
Surya, it didn't turn out as we planned.
I don't get it.
Both of them are looking for you now.
Anything might happen at any time.
You also said your sister is pregnant.
Let's not risk it.
Listen to me.
-Leave town urgently.
-And?
They won't spare me
anyway once they identify me.
What were you planning on doing then?
Whoever that guy is,
in a way he helped us a lot, sir.
Even if we don't find him,
we could take a phony to
your brother in his place.
We'll hit the jackpot, sir.
Why didn't I think of this?
-What was that?
-Jackpot, sir.
-How does it feel?
-It hurts, sir.
It hurts like hell, sir.
Wipe it. Here you go.
-Did the pain go down?
-No, sir. No.
Money doesn't heal the pain, does it?
No, sir.
Then how will I…
He hit me, Sudha.
And you say he helped us?!
He raised his hand.
He was about to punch me.
But then he stopped.
Walked away.
Came back and punched me this time.
Why did he stop the first time?
Why did he come back and punch me?
What happened in the meantime?
Hey!
What has he done?
There's some connection between
the clock and landing the punch.
-We need to find out.
-I'll figure it out, sir.
-So, you checked it.
-Sir.
The clock is ten minutes ahead.
Sir.
So what if it's ten minutes ahead?
-Sir… I don't know.
-You don't know?
He didn't know either.
He assumed the clock
struck twelve and stopped.
When he found out,
he came back to punch me.
So what if the clock struck twelve?
The day just changed, sir.
It's a Sunday then.
So he doesn't hit on Sundays?
Who would be so weird, sir?
I'm sure he's capable of that.
Who is it, Sudha?
The guy who hit you
also wore a mask, right?
He put a mask on me and hit me, sir.
Whatever! He hit you, right?
-Yes, sir.
-What day was it?
I think it's on 25th…
Enough of your English!
I'll break your jaw!
What day was it?
-Friday or Saturday… It was the…
-Twenty…
-It was the 24th.
-Saturday!
Absolutely, sir.
Saturday.
He hit the both of us on a Saturday.
There are two possibilities, Sudha.
He either stays under
the radar on Sundays…
and goes all out from Monday to Saturday.
Or…
He goes all out only on Saturdays.
-Now it makes sense, Sudha.
-Sir…
I want details about FIRs filed
on Saturdays in all the stations.
Okay, sir.
It's enough indeed.
Saturday is enough.
Sir, I inquired everywhere.
No complaint has been registered.
But there was one
complaint at the last station.
-When?
-Just now.
Sir.
Hey!
What are you looking at?
Sir.
Tell me.
My name is Surya, sir.
-A guy hit me. I want to file…
-Who hit you?
I don't know, sir.
I don't know.
Sir, sir, sir.
When? Which day was it?
Last Saturday, sir.
Time?
Around 10:30 p.m. when
I was returning from work.
-Where do you work?
-NLIC, sir.
NLIC.
-Government employee?
-Yes, sir.
ID?
Sir.
-Sudha, check it.
-Sir.
-Date?
-Check it.
-Sir?
-The date when he hit you.
The date was…
Twenty-second…
What?
Twenty-second.
Twenty-second?
-Sudha, I got him. Open the cell.
-Sir…
Hey!
Open the cell.
Twenty-second is a government holiday.
-Not a working day.
-Sir, sir, sir.
-Sir, hear me out.
-Get in!
-Hey!
-Sir, please! No!
Sir, please, sir!
It's not him.
I assumed he must've put
his criminal mind to use…
by hitting me and then
going on to file a complaint.
All this in the hopes of protecting
himself from me, I thought.
But he's not that smart.
Su…
-Surya.
-Surya…
Was he wearing the mask
or did he force one on you?
He was wearing the mask, sir.
How do you know?
How do I know?
You also got hit.
What are you laughing at, idiot?
I feel like I've seen you somewhere.
I told you about the petrol
leak at the hospital, sir.
-GH?
-Yes, sir.
-Sudha, do you remember him?
Then why didn't you say so?
Surya, thank you.
Come, sit.
Surya, let's be open.
-Sir.
-The guy who hit you, him…
and me…
is the same person.
He hit you?!
Don't be so shocked. That's the truth.
-Surya.
-Sir.
Surya, I couldn't see
his face in the dark.
Did you see anything to help identify him?
I tried my best to see his face, sir.
I can recognize his eyes though.
-Confirm?
-Yes, sir.
Sudha, whoever fits the description
in that age group, get them.
-We should definitely get him!
-Yes!
Surya, usually I hit
people without a reason.
But a guy hit me without reason.
Will I spare him?
Wait and watch.
I will…
You know what I'll do to
his family in front of his eyes?
I won't tell you.
Because I don't know what I'm going to do.
-Charulatha!
-Sir.
Take his details.
Come, Surya.
I've seen people who don't eat
non-veg or drink on Saturdays.
What's with hitting and killing people?
Do you think it's some sort of worship?
We've identified ten men
in the same age group.
Call the NLIC guy.
Sir.
You took his number, right? Call him!
No, sir.
Bottle Cap?
Why does it say "Bottle Cap"?
His face looks a little like a bottle cap.
You don't give it away.
But you're very naughty.
Hello.
Don't say Charu. Don't say Charu.
Please.
Hello, Charulatha ma'am.
Brother, Daya here.
No, sir.
Well…
where was I supposed to be on
the Saturday he tried to kill me?
Delhi, sir.
Sir.
We found him!
Hello.
I found a guy here.
I have a feeling it's him.
You found the guy?
Why? Did you also find the guy?
I don't know if the guy
you found is the guy.
But the guy I found is definitely the guy.
-Come, we'll talk.
-Coming, brother.
Your brother seems to be real fast, sir.
Come, dear.
He's the guy.
I'll handle him.
Hey, Surya!
What?
Get up!
Hey, you know him?
-Don't be silly, brother.
-No, it's him!
-It's not him.
-I'm telling you, it's him!
-Trust me, it's not him.
-Oh, dear! Please believe me.
I thought really hard
and got hold of him.
My judgment says he's the guy.
Foolish judgment.
He's also a victim of the
Saturday guy just like us.
In fact, only he has sort of seen him.
We found the actual guy.
He should take a look and confirm it.
You found him?
-Sudha!
-Sir.
What's this?
Sorry, Surya.
Sir, the real guy…
Take a look.
What is this?
He's one of the Sokulapalem guys.
He wrote a message on the wall.
Is this him?
Let me go, sir!
No, sir.
-Is this him?
-No, sir.
Is that him?
Surya, look properly!
Kill them!
Is it him?
-Is it him?
-No, sir.
-Surya, look properly!
-No, sir!
-Tell me!
-Hey!
Men aged between
20-35 come forward.
Come on, Surya.
How can you not identify him now?
He's supposed to be here, right?
They're painting his
portrait and celebrating.
I'm definite he's not among them, sir.
-Sudha!
-Sir.
-Check who's missing from the list.
Sir, so many of us went
out of town for work.
Went out of town…
Who all?
-So many of them.
-I want them all to come back right now!
How can they suddenly…
-Give us four to five days.
-Hey!
Two days.
Two days. Yeah.
They should be here in two days.
Just two days.
I was worried about your safety
in case I told you I did all this.
But not telling you
meant risking your lives.
I don't get it, Dad.
Forget about us.
If you tell them that it's you…
what's the point of
everything you've done so far?
Even when your uncle abused
your aunt, she'd be meek.
She feared him.
The kind of fear the
people of Sokulapalem have.
Your mom had the kind of anger you do now.
What did she do?
She assured your aunt that
she could survive on her own.
She only gave her courage.
Knowingly or unknowingly…
you're walking in your mom's footsteps.
How can you stop halfway now?
Finish this the way you're meant to.
Listen.
I just had an epiphany.
Maybe these were the last
words your mom wanted to tell you.
True anger isn't that which…
makes a few people fear you.
It is that which
empowers a group of people.
Even he doesn't know.
He's torturing Surya because he
was there when Daya was beaten.
Daya will not spare
you till he finds the guy.
If we want to save ourselves,
we should find out
who the Saturday guy is.
Think about how to achieve that.
Which quality do you
guys have in common?
Fear?
Fear.
Daya is looking for the
scaredy-cat among you.
The Saturday guy would be
scared because he hit Daya.
But why are you guys scared?
So, you being courageous isn't enough.
Each one of you should be more
courageous than the person beside you.
That's it!
Show the same courage.
The Saturday guy will be found.
-They'll kill him once they find him.
-Let them!
What's your problem?
Why do we care if he dies?
We'll get him caught, go
inside, and weep like always.
-Simple, right?
-That was before.
Now we have mustered some courage.
It's better to use that courage to
protect him rather than get him caught.
When the Saturday guy wrote
on the wall for the first time,
we got hope that it was one
of us who was fighting for us.
When we got beaten because of him,
we got angry with him.
Now, in an attempt to get him caught,
we got courage as well.
He brought so many
changes in us unknowingly.
-Such a guy…
-What do you plan on doing then?
He took a step forward for all of us.
Now we'll take a step forward for him.
He has a big plan if he has
chosen to unite so many people.
Plan? What plan?
Mobile data plan.
What is it, Brother?
Nothing.
Something struck me
this morning while praying.
How do you know that the Saturday
guy tried to kill me at the pub?
How did you arrive at the right time?
I've been guarding your
life every second, brother.
And then this guy shows
up and gives me hell.
Sir!
-Sudha!
-Sir.
How come we didn't doubt this?
How did the Saturday guy
know that we were at the pub?
Yes, sir.
In fact, we didn't plan on
going until the last minute.
Exactly!
Who else knows about the plan?
The lawyer?
He's not capable of that.
Sir, me? No way!
-Sorry.
-Sir, perfume?
-Sir.
-You took his number, right?
Call the NLIC guy.
Charulatha!
It's her!
She's helping the Saturday guy.
What the…
But, who do you think he is?
We need to figure out who he is.
Bottle Cap.
Bottle Cap!
Surya!
He's the Saturday guy.
Bloody hell!
He was right beside me the whole time.
My brother's judgment was right, Sudha!
Brother!
We found him!
Your judgment is right!
It is him!
You're right.
We found him.
But my judgment is wrong.
-Sir!
-Brother…
The Saturday guy got away.
I saw his face.
It's Surya!
-Surya?!
-Yes, sir.
When will Dad be here?
He'll be here before you go into labor.
Hello, sir.
Hello, brother.
I made you a promise, remember?
I'll destroy his family in front
of his eyes when I find him.
I know you remember.
No more hide and seek.
I found him.
And I started my
streak with his girlfriend.
Say something.
Charu?
Hey, Bottle Cap!
Do you understand?
Come fast. I'm waiting.
Surya!
SATURDAY
Aunty, Charu…
Surya…
Aunty…
It's me, Chinnu.
Chinnu?
Chinnu…
-Aunty…
-I didn't think I'd see you again.
So Charu is…
Kallu?
Kallu!
My patience has worn out.
My tears have dried out.
Understood?
Come.
SOKULAPALEM
Come, come!
Sudha…
I took him for an innocent
guy due to his performance.
But I turned out to be the
innocent one in this story.
He played me.
Hey! Show me your performance now.
Let's see how natural it is.
You've played a big game.
REDEMPTION
Seems like she lost a lot of blood.
She needs to go to the hospital.
Will you take her?
But I have a condition.
See these people?
If at least one of them…
opens the door and displays
the courage you gave them…
I'll personally take her to the hospital.
Okay?
Get up!
Call them!
Rajanna…
If you don't step out now, you never will.
Laxman!
The courage you wanted
to see isn't here with us.
Let me show you what fear does!
Hey!
Come on out, everyone!
Why are you standing?
He'll mistake it for courage.
Kneel down! Come on!
I was hoping he'd show
me who the Saturday guy is.
But instead, I'm telling you
that he's the Saturday guy.
What's even funnier is,
he was going to bring out
your courage by hitting me.
Am I right?
Come!
You'll give them courage?
Answer me!
-How much?
-Two hundred rupees.
Two hundred? It's nearby.
I brought you into the lane, sir.
Sir, do you have change for 500 rupees?
I guess he doesn't.
Alright. Keep this.
It's Kallu, Dad.
What?
Sit down, sir.
You might not be able to sit again.
Sudha…
He's losing his shit
watching his son like this.
No, sir.
He and I, we're used to this.
Come.
You just met him.
You need to know who he is as a person.
He's not the type to project
his anger on someone else.
From the moment he feels anger,
he writes down the person's
name, introspects his anger,
and if he still feels that
his anger is justified,
he schedules that person's
wrath for that Saturday.
No matter who it is.
In fact, he was angry at you as well.
The first time, when he was
going to write your name down,
Charu…
He stopped because of her thought.
You got saved.
He wrote your name down the second time.
But, I…
I gave him sleeping pills and stopped him.
I kind of saved you.
Killing all chances of ever
writing your name down again…
my daughter made him promise
to quit these Saturday fights.
She completely saved you.
You owe your life to our family, sir.
For saving you from this beast.
So, I'm alive today because
of the promise he made to his sister?
Sudha, it's funny how I got out alive
so many times without my involvement.
Something else also happened
without your involvement.
Surya.
Remember what Mom used to say?
"The day your anger is truly
justified, I won't say a word."
Dad told me everything.
Today is your day.
I won't say a word.
She gave you permission.
What are you waiting for?
That's what I don't understand, sir.
When he decides to
hit a guy every Saturday…
I go to them and warn them beforehand.
Similarly, I came to warn you.
But here, he's on the floor.
I called him a beast before.
No, sir.
He's a changed man.
There's no place he hasn't
looked for his aunt and Kallu.
Kallu is the love of his life.
They're the lives his mother
has preciously guarded.
Despite that, when you touched
Kallu, my daughter-in-law,
he calmed his anger down,
waiting for their lives to change,
for them to muster courage.
He's a changed man, sir.
You're one lucky man, sir.
Look.
The people of Sokulapalem
are protecting you now.
By chance of luck,
even if one of them musters the
courage and takes a step forward…
you've only seen his two
eyes at the pub that day.
You'll see his third eye now.
It's going to be Shiva Tandavam.
So, if I want to see the
Saturday guy you're talking about…
one of them has to
courageously step forward?
Yes, sir.
These fools aren't coming
forward no matter what I do.
What should I do?
Sir, please let her go.
She's a little girl.
Please let her go.
Sir, let her go! Please!
Sir, please let her go.
If I kill this little girl…
would that be enough?
Keep them coming!
This is not enough!
That's enough!
He, the one who breaks
The shackles of doubt
With a fierce and intense gaze
His nails are like blazing
Flames on a mountain
He is the constant force
Of balance on a Saturday
The battlefield is ready for war
Let the conch shells echo in the air
Even your eyes launch weapons
Your blood boils with the fuel of breath
The warrior of ferocity burns wild
The war bells ring with an echo
There is fire flaring up all around
It is going to be Shiva Tandavam
The warrior of ferocity burns wild
The war bells ring with an echo
There is fire flaring up all around
It is going to be Shiva Tandavam
You guys go, ma'am!
You can't leave without telling
me how the performance was!
Oh, no!
You need to go to the hospital.
Will you go?
But I have one condition.
If at least one of them…
comes forward and says…
"Poor guy, Surya! Let him go."
I'll personally take you to the hospital.
Okay?
Go ahead. Ask!
There lived a demon called
Narakasur in the olden days.
He used to trouble people a lot.
So Sri Krishna teamed up with Satyabhama…
and killed him.
Those were the olden days.
Back then.
These are modern times.
We can't keep waiting for
new avatars and heroes.
We should stand up for ourselves.
Mankind should help each other.
We have to be there for one another.
No matter who the opposite person is.
There's action in my life.
There's emotion and suspense.
There's everything, in fact.
Except for romance.
You've known me for a while.
Didn't you ever have feelings for me?
For your "Bottle Cap" face?
-Surya…
-Yes, Dad!
Your "Scooty Pep" face got
lucky with this "Bottle Cap."
Nani.
Did you call me, Samantha?
I'm feeling like you're calling me,
even though you aren't.
I can imagine how special I am to you.
You said your mom was going to
be reborn as your sister's daughter.
We're forever in agreement now.
We'll abide by whatever your mom says.
I got angry.
And once I get angry,
they become my family.
And this becomes my problem.
I won't spare them.
I won't spare any of them.